<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sun Jul  8 07:19:12 2012 -->
<channel id="bbc1" source="XMLTV" date="13/07/2012">
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team. Also in HD. [S] Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes past each hour.</desc>
<title>Breakfast</title>
<end>0915</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>25/25. Series following the work of probate researchers. The team search for living relatives of widower Gordon Smith, who died in 2009, leaving behind an estate worth 150,000 pounds.</desc>
<title>Heir Hunters</title>
<end>1000</end>
<start>0915</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Martin Roberts and Lucy Alexander visit a flat on the Isle of Bute, a one-bed property in London and a ground floor flat in Norwich. [S] Then BBC News; Weather.</desc>
<title>Homes Under the Hammer</title>
<end>1100</end>
<start>1000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Clive Holland has help for those who have fallen victim to cowboy builders. The team help two women living near each other who suffered big financial losses thanks to one builder.</desc>
<title>Cowboy Trap</title>
<end>1145</end>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>10/10. Gloria Hunniford goes back to school for lesson, led by Cambridgeshire Police, revealing the dangers of doorstep crime. Also in HD. [S] Then BBC News; Weather.</desc>
<title>Doorstep Crime 999</title>
<end>1215</end>
<start>1145</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Stamford</subtitle>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The antiques challenge comes from Stamford in Lincolnshire, with experts Catherine Southon and Nick Hall. One of the antiques meets an undignified end at auction.</desc>
<title>Bargain Hunt</title>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1215</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather.</desc>
<title>BBC News at One</title>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather for the Midlands.</desc>
<title>Midlands Today</title>
<end>1345</end>
<start>1330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Head Screwed On</subtitle>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Zara dreads a duty lunch with her aunt and uncle but is shocked to discover they are not as dull as she thought. Meanwhile, Mandy returns to work. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Doctors</title>
<end>1415</end>
<start>1345</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Suffolk</subtitle>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Property series. Denise Nurse helps a couple find a home with plenty of character in Suffolk. With a budget of 450,000 pounds, the buyers are seeking three bedrooms.</desc>
<title>Escape to the Country</title>
<end>1500</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather.</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<end>1505</end>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>CBBC. Making of Alaska and South America: Wildlife series. Steve Backshall looks at the challenges faced when filming in the frozen tundra of Alaska and the steaming rainforests of Brazil.</desc>
<title>Deadly 60</title>
<end>1535</end>
<start>1505</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>CBBC. Space Disaster: Chantal invites her friend Isabella to be a cadet for a day at Space Program Australia. [S] Then Diddy Dick and Dom.</desc>
<title>Prank Patrol Down Under</title>
<end>1600</end>
<start>1535</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>CBBC. Sam and Mark host as two families battle it out in a range of hilarious games, like Quick on the Draw, Mime Time, Music Round, and the formidable Copycats Challenge. Also in HD.</desc>
<title>Copycats</title>
<end>1630</end>
<start>1600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>CBBC. Helen and Barney show you how you can upcycle odd gloves left over from winter into fabulous new toys and Kieron Richardson reveals his favourite children's book. Also in HD.</desc>
<title>Blue Peter</title>
<end>1700</end>
<start>1630</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>CBBC. Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
<title>Newsround</title>
<end>1715</end>
<start>1700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Quiz in which contestants try to score as few points as possible by plumbing the depths of their general knowledge to come up with the answers no-one else can think of.</desc>
<title>Pointless</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1715</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather.</desc>
<title>BBC News at Six</title>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather for the Midlands.</desc>
<title>Midlands Today</title>
<end>1900</end>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Matt Baker and Chris Evans bring you the stories that matter from across the country. Also in HD.</desc>
<title>The One Show</title>
<end>1930</end>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>A compilation of the best bits from the sports quiz. Regulars Sue Barker, Matt Dawson and Phil Tufnell are joined by guests including Michael Owen. Also in HD. [S] Then BBC News.</desc>
<title>A Question of Sport</title>
<end>2000</end>
<start>1930</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Phil is furious when Jay and Ben confess the truth about their recent actions, and points out that things could soon be over for them all as a result. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>EastEnders</title>
<end>2030</end>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>3/9. Rob Brydon hosts the comedy panel show, with team captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack, and guest panelists David O'Doherty, Katherine Parkinson, Bill Turnbull and Louie Spence. Also in HD.</desc>
<title>Would I Lie to You?</title>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>6/10. Objects of Desire: Drama. A murder investigation reunites DSI Sandra Pullman with an old flame, DCI James Larson. Meanwhile, Brian Lane faces a domestic crisis. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>New Tricks</title>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The latest national and international news, with reports from BBC correspondents worldwide.</desc>
<title>BBC News at Ten</title>
<end>2225</end>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>The latest news, sport and weather for the Midlands. [S] Followed by national weather.</desc>
<title>Midlands Today</title>
<end>2235</end>
<start>2225</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>2/6. Sunderland: Stand-up from the Sunderland Empire Theatre. Michael introduces Simon Evans, Jimeoin, Imran Yusuf and headliner Sarah Millican. Contains adult humour.  Also in HD.</desc>
<title>Michael McIntyre's Comedy Roadshow</title>
<end>2320</end>
<start>2235</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>...Night Draws. The National Lottery Friday night draws presented by Scott Mills. Includes Thunderball, EuroMillions and the UK Millionaire Raffle, with a guaranteed prize of a million pounds.</desc>
<title>The National Lottery Friday...</title>
<end>2330</end>
<start>2320</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>5/6. They Think It's All Over: Ollie can't celebrate his birthday when he is dropped from his football team. Contains adult humour.  Also in HD.</desc>
<title>White Van Man</title>
<end>0000</end>
<start>2330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Masood is stunned when his wayward brother AJ arrives on the Square, but it soon becomes clear why Zainab is not a fan. Kat's efforts to spend time alone with Alfie are thwarted. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>EastEnders</title>
<end>0155</end>
<start>0000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc>
<title>Weatherview</title>
<end>0200</end>
<start>0155</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>3/3. Documentary series. Summer arrives, bringing with it wedding season at Chatsworth, but there is a veil hanging over proceedings and it does not belong to the bride. [AD,S,SL]</desc>
<title>Chatsworth</title>
<end>0300</end>
<start>0200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Presenter Jasmine Harman calls on expert assistance to help her mother and other chronic hoarders combat the condition that is ruining their lives and those of their families. [S,SL]</desc>
<title>Britain's Biggest Hoarders</title>
<end>0400</end>
<start>0300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>South West Judging</subtitle>
<flags></flags>
<desc>It's decision time for the chefs from the South West region. Two remain to cook their entire menus for judges Prue Leith, Matthew Fort and Oliver Peyton. [S,SL]</desc>
<title>Great British Menu</title>
<end>0430</end>
<start>0400</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news, with bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes.</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0430</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
