<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sun Jul  8 07:19:21 2012 -->
<channel id="bbc2" source="XMLTV" date="13/07/2012">
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Moon and Snowboarding: Pingu welcomes viewers to his secret whale-shaped funhouse for another show. The episodes are Pingu's Moon Adventure and Robby the Snowboarder. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Zigby's Magic Trick: The adventures of Zigby the Zebra and his friends. Zigby gets into all sorts of trouble when he agrees to make McMeer disappear! [S]</desc>
<title>Zigby</title>
<end>0625</end>
<start>0610</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Timmy Makes a Splash: Animated adventures of a young lamb at nursery school. Everyone is having fun in the paddling pool, until Stripey pulls the stopper out of the valve. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Timmy Time</title>
<end>0635</end>
<start>0625</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Bees: Animated series about dirtgirl and her friends. Keen to find out how bees help in the garden, dirtgirl sets about making a sweet-pea teepee to attract them. [S]</desc>
<title>dirtgirlworld</title>
<end>0650</end>
<start>0635</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Da Bag A Bling: Stop-motion series featuring a crime-fighting special agent who plays in a reggae band. The Easy Crew track down a bredda with a wicked hip hop vibe. [S]</desc>
<title>Rastamouse</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0650</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Animal action with Johny Pitts and Rani Price. The wildest horses in the world need their hooves trimming - but how do you catch them? The tiger cubs take their dinner by the pool. [S]</desc>
<title>Roar</title>
<end>0730</end>
<start>0700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. LOSE vs Lair: Frogg upgrades the Lair security system to protect Voltar's sweet new bike. [S] Followed by Leon.</desc>
<title>League of Super Evil</title>
<end>0745</end>
<start>0730</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Hay Day: Animation about the friendship between Lottie, a misfit, and Nine, a cat. The pinnacle of the Oddsburg Hay Day celebrations is a hay sculpting competition. [S] Followed by The Owl.</desc>
<title>Frankenstein's Cat</title>
<end>0800</end>
<start>0745</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. 20/20. Wildlife show. Jamie and Izak dig up a porker of a problem and Kat and Phoebe face up to a one-eyed horse. [S]</desc>
<title>Dick 'N' Dom Go Wild</title>
<end>0830</end>
<start>0800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 19/25. Making Music: Show for preschool children. Joel wants to make music, so Nina helps him find household objects that he can use as instruments. They then go to see a real band. [S]</desc>
<title>Nina and the Neurons</title>
<end>0845</end>
<start>0830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. A Room With A View: The comic adventures of two unlikely best friends. Big and Small race each other to build a mountain in their garden so they will have a view from their window. [S]</desc>
<title>Big and Small</title>
<end>0900</end>
<start>0845</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Why Snake Has No Legs: Stories telling a young audience how different animals got their distinctive parts. Snake had hundreds of legs, until he swapped them all for Millipede's eyes. [S]</desc>
<title>Tinga Tinga Tales</title>
<end>0910</end>
<start>0900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 12/13. Charley Bounces Nibblit: Series about a teddy bear with a big imagination. Charley becomes a show business impresario presenting his greatest act - Nibblit! [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Little Charley Bear</title>
<end>0920</end>
<start>0910</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Gone Fishing: Animation featuring Raa Raa, who lives in the Jingly Jangly Jungle. Raa Raa is keen to try fishing, but keeps scaring the fish away every time he makes a noise. [S]</desc>
<title>Raa Raa the Noisy Lion</title>
<end>0930</end>
<start>0920</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 11/15. Spud's Straw Surprise: Cartoon adventures of builder Bob and his friends. Spud thinks Farmer Pickles and Bob are building a new super-sized scarecrow out of straw to replace him. [S]</desc>
<title>Bob the Builder: Project Build It</title>
<end>0940</end>
<start>0930</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Josie's Knotty Problem: Frank and Buster are two intrepid koalas who fly around on a mission to help other creatures. Josie's shoelaces keep coming undone and she can't tie them. [S]</desc>
<title>The Koala Brothers</title>
<end>0950</end>
<start>0940</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. March of the Fluffies: Preschool stop-frame animation. The Fluffies are on an unstoppable march towards a deep canyon, so the team have to find something to act as a bridge. [S]</desc>
<title>Lunar Jim</title>
<end>1000</end>
<start>0950</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sticky: Series in which a drawn line creates challenges and surprises for the unsuspecting Dipdap. Dipdap is caught in a sticky mess when the Line draws some bubblegum. [S]</desc>
<title>Dipdap</title>
<end>1005</end>
<start>1000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Planet Shout: Children's quiz. Snout's home planet is a place of sprouts and crackling, sneezing craters. Will he try to help Twist win the race or look for his nephews? [S]</desc>
<title>Kerwhizz</title>
<end>1030</end>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sky High Loopy: Driver Dan goes on an exciting journey to Story Corner. Everyone watches in amazement to see if Loopy can become a flying dinosaur. [S]</desc>
<title>Driver Dan's Story Train</title>
<end>1040</end>
<start>1030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Jumpybug: Animated series set in the magical land of Nara. Yojojo is surprised when a Jumpybug suddenly appears. He and the other Piplings play jumping games with it. [S]</desc>
<title>Waybuloo</title>
<end>1100</end>
<start>1040</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Windy Day in the Garden: Series for young children. On a very windy day, Igglepiggle's blanket is blown into the air and the Tombliboos' trousers are blown off the line. [S]</desc>
<title>In the Night Garden</title>
<end>1130</end>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The latest international news from the BBC. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC World News</title>
<end>1200</end>
<start>1130</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Andrew Neil has the top political stories of the day. [S]</desc>
<title>Daily Politics</title>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>7/15. St Paul's Cathedral: Dr Jonathan Foyle scales Britain's most iconic structures to reveal the buildings' secrets. Jonathan's journey takes him to St Paul's Cathedral in London. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Climbing Great Buildings</title>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Glossop</subtitle>
<desc>Property series. The most specific budget ever comes to town as Ed Hall and Jonnie Irwin seek a home in Glossop. [S]</desc>
<title>To Buy or Not to Buy</title>
<end>1415</end>
<start>1330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Anne Robinson presents the quick-fire general knowledge quiz in which contestants must decide at the end of each round which of their number should be eliminated. [S]</desc>
<title>The Weakest Link</title>
<end>1500</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>5/15. Competition for a spot at a grand exhibition at the Royal College of Art, this time featuring a freelance illustrator, an amateur sculptor and a part-time art restorer. [S]</desc>
<title>Show Me the Monet</title>
<end>1545</end>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Britain. Oxfordshire: Si King and Dave Myers explore Oxfordshire, where they resurrect a lost county recipe and cook it for the locals in Henley, and make cheese with rock star Alex James. [S]</desc>
<title>The Hairy Bikers' Food Tour of...</title>
<end>1630</end>
<start>1545</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Bury St Edmunds</subtitle>
<desc>Flog It! comes from Bury St Edmunds, where David Barby and Adam Partridge offer up their antiques expertise. Paul Martin visits Thorpe Abbots airbase. [S]</desc>
<title>Flog It!</title>
<end>1715</end>
<start>1630</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>On the final leg of the road trip Jonathan and Charles visit Blackpool, Morecambe and Kendal. Jonathan is distracted by items he cannot afford. [S]</desc>
<title>Antiques Road Trip</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1715</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>John Inverdale introduces live coverage of the first of two days of competition at Crystal Palace as the world's best athletes fine tune their preparations for the London Olympics. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Athletics: London Grand Prix</title>
<end>2030</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The 118th BBC Proms gets under way at the Royal Albert Hall with a concert of English music by Elgar, Delius, Tippett and Mark-Anthony Turnage. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>First Night of the Proms</title>
<end>2230</end>
<start>2030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In-depth investigation and analysis of the stories behind the day's headlines with Eddie Mair. [S] Followed by weather.</desc>
<title>Newsnight</title>
<end>2305</end>
<start>2230</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Hazel Irvine introduces highlights of the second round's play at the Scottish Open, the traditional warm-up event for the Open Championship. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Golf: Scottish Open Highlights</title>
<end>0005</end>
<start>2305</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Edith Bowman and Greg James present highlights from Scotland's biggest music festival T in the Park, including performances from Kasabian, Tinie Tempah, Professor Green and Jessie J. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>T in the Park Highlights</title>
<end>0205</end>
<start>0005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>BBC Two joins the BBC's rolling news channel, with bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<end>0405</end>
<start>0205</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>and information from the BBC's Teletext service. New.</desc>
<title>Pages from Ceefax</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0405</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Scooter and Box: Pingu welcomes viewers to his secret whale-shaped funhouse for sketches, penguin facts and two classic episodes, Pingu's New Scooter and Pingu and the Box. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
