<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sun Jul  8 07:24:46 2012 -->
<channel id="film_four" source="XMLTV" date="13/07/2012">
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>1100</end>
<start>0700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Randolph Scott plays a bounty hunter on the trail of three murderers who robbed a train. However, his investigation uncovers some murky secrets in the town of Twin Forks.</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>The Bounty Hunter</title>
<year>1954</year>
<end>1235</end>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>John Wayne stars as a moody young man living in the Ozarks who has sworn revenge on his long-absent father for deserting his mother. Then a kindly stranger appears on the scene...</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>The Shepherd of the Hills</title>
<year>1941</year>
<end>1430</end>
<start>1235</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>In Cy Endfield's epic 1890s-set drama, Michael Caine and Stanley Baker play two British officers charged with defending Rorke's Drift from a force of 4000 Zulus. War violence.</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>Zulu</title>
<year>1964</year>
<end>1715</end>
<start>1430</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>James Cameron talks about the creation of the planet Pandora for his new film Avatar.</desc>
<title>Avatar Special</title>
<end>1720</end>
<start>1715</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Raquel Welch - in her famous fur bikini - stars in this prehistoric adventure set in an inhospitable landscape populated by roving dinosaurs and two warring tribes.</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>One Million Years B.C.</title>
<year>1966</year>
<end>1915</end>
<start>1720</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Wes Anderson's acclaimed and witty stop-motion animated version of Roald Dahl's children's classic. With the voices of George Clooney, Meryl Streep, Owen Wilson and Jarvis Cocker.  [AD,S]</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>Fantastic Mr. Fox</title>
<year>2009</year>
<end>2100</end>
<start>1915</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Romantic comedy. Cameron Diaz and Ashton Kutcher meet in Las Vegas. Together they get very drunk, marry and win a fortune. Then their troubles really begin...  [AD,S]</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>What Happens in Vegas</title>
<year>2008</year>
<end>2255</end>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Violent supernatural horror starring Arnold Schwarzenegger as a run-down, alcoholic ex-cop, who takes on The Devil himself.</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>End of Days</title>
<year>1999</year>
<end>0115</end>
<start>2255</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>The alien Predator is back, hunting the streets of Los Angeles for his prey. But when he starts taking on the police, Danny Glover gets tough. Strong language/violence.</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>Predator 2</title>
<year>1990</year>
<end>0325</end>
<start>0115</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>...Special</subtitle>
<flags>(S)</flags>
<desc>Andrew Garfield, Emma Stone, Rhys Ifans and director Marc Webb talk about bringing the new version of Spider-Man to the screen.</desc>
<title>Amazing Spider-Man Interview...</title>
<end>0335</end>
<start>0325</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<flags></flags>
<desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
<title>Teleshopping</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0335</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
