<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Jul 11 08:39:24 2012 -->
<channel id="bbc2" source="XMLTV" date="11/07/2012">
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Litter and Big Catch: Animation. Pingu welcomes viewers to his whale-shaped funhouse for sketches, penguin facts and two classic episodes, Pingu and the Litter and Pingu's Big Catch. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Zigby's Parrot: The adventures of Zigby the Zebra and his friends. It is McMeer's birthday and Zigby and Bertie want to give him the best birthday ever. [S]</desc>
<title>Zigby</title>
<end>0625</end>
<start>0610</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Timmy's Pet Problem: Animated adventures of a young lamb at nursery school. Timmy finds an old mop head and is convinced that it is a little animal, which he adopts as his pet. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Timmy Time</title>
<end>0635</end>
<start>0625</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Dig: Animated series about dirtgirl and her friends, who live in a bizarre world. You can squeeze a lot into a morning: dirtgirl digs a pond for her new froggy friends. [S]</desc>
<title>dirtgirlworld</title>
<end>0650</end>
<start>0635</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Double Crossin' Diva: Stop-motion series featuring a crime-fighting special agent who plays in a reggae band. When a minibus goes missing, Rastamouse investigates. [S]</desc>
<title>Rastamouse</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0650</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Animal action with Johny Pitts and Rani Price. There is snarling and hissing as a pair of very rare Chinese leopards arrive at the park. [S]</desc>
<title>Roar</title>
<end>0730</end>
<start>0700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Slam Dunked: Voltar is denied entry to the neighbourhood slam dunk competition for being too short. [S] Followed by Leon.</desc>
<title>League of Super Evil</title>
<end>0745</end>
<start>0730</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Film: A horror film director is in town making a low-budget epic, and he's cast Lottie and Nine. [S] Followed by The Owl.</desc>
<title>Frankenstein's Cat</title>
<end>0800</end>
<start>0745</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. 18/20. Wildlife show. Jack and Thomas help a greyhound with a sore tail, while Jake and Cameron look after a poorly bat. [S]</desc>
<title>Dick 'N' Dom Go Wild</title>
<end>0830</end>
<start>0800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 17/25. Different Tastes: Show for preschool children. Eilidh wants to know why her dad likes bacon and banana sandwiches. Nina and Eilidh find out about different flavours. [S]</desc>
<title>Nina and the Neurons</title>
<end>0845</end>
<start>0830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Friends in a Fog: The comic adventures of two unlikely best friends. Big and Small sail off to explore the pond but find themselves lost in a fog. [S]</desc>
<title>Big and Small</title>
<end>0900</end>
<start>0845</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Why Crocodile Has a Bumpy Back: Stories telling young children how animals got their distinctive parts. Here, the story of how Crocodile got his bumpy back and became grumpy. [S]</desc>
<title>Tinga Tinga Tales</title>
<end>0910</end>
<start>0900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 10/13. The Charleysaurus: Series about a teddy bear with a big imagination. Charley and Midge go exploring to try to find some dinosaurs, and they soon find a Charleysaurus. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Little Charley Bear</title>
<end>0920</end>
<start>0910</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Something New: Animation featuring Raa Raa, who lives in the Jingly Jangly Jungle. Raa Raa is looking for something new in the Jingly Jangly Jungle. [S]</desc>
<title>Raa Raa the Noisy Lion</title>
<end>0930</end>
<start>0920</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 9/15. Two Scoops: Animated adventures with Bob the Builder and all his friends as they construct a new, ecologically friendly town from scratch. Robert gets a machine called Benny. [S]</desc>
<title>Bob the Builder: Project Build It</title>
<end>0940</end>
<start>0930</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Ned and the Wagaloo: The adventures of two intrepid young koalas. Ned sets off to find a legendary creature but forgets to tell his friends where he's going. [S]</desc>
<title>The Koala Brothers</title>
<end>0950</end>
<start>0940</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. The Leaf Thief: Preschool stop-frame animation set on the second-to-last moon of the Milky Way. It is a very hot day and the gang find that the leaves from the moon trees are gone. [S]</desc>
<title>Lunar Jim</title>
<end>1000</end>
<start>0950</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sad Thing: Series in which a drawn line creates challenges for the unsuspecting little character, Dipdap. The line draws a very sad thing. Dipdap does his best to cheer it up. [S]</desc>
<title>Dipdap</title>
<end>1005</end>
<start>1000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Treasure Island Trail: Children's quiz. The Kerwhizz teams are tempted by the lure of Long Pong Silver's Treasure. Will they race, or seek the place where the hoard is hidden? [S]</desc>
<title>Kerwhizz</title>
<end>1030</end>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Treasure Adventure: Driver Dan goes on an exciting journey to Story Corner. It's Driver Dan's Treasure Hunt and there are lots of clues for the Story Train friends to solve. [S]</desc>
<title>Driver Dan's Story Train</title>
<end>1040</end>
<start>1030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Catch the Plumato: Animated series set in the magical land of Nara. De Li rests under a plumato tree and a plumato falls in her lap. [S]</desc>
<title>Waybuloo</title>
<end>1100</end>
<start>1040</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Trousers on the Ninky Nonk: Children's programme. The Tombliboos and Makka Pakka take a ride on the Ninky Nonk. [S]</desc>
<title>In the Night Garden</title>
<end>1130</end>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Andrew Neil and Jo Coburn present live coverage of Prime Minister's Questions and the latest political news, interviews and debate. [S]</desc>
<title>Daily Politics</title>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1130</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>5/15. Layer Marney Tower: Dr Jonathan Foyle scales Britain's most iconic structures to reveal the buildings' secrets. The next step in Jonathan's journey takes him to Layer Marney Tower. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Climbing Great Buildings</title>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Property series. Ed Hall and Jonny Benarr come to the aid of a man forced to house hunt with his mother in law in Stamford. [S]</desc>
<title>To Buy or Not to Buy</title>
<end>1415</end>
<start>1330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Anne Robinson presents the quick-fire general knowledge quiz in which contestants must decide at the end of each round which of their number should be eliminated. [S]</desc>
<title>The Weakest Link</title>
<end>1500</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/15. Competition for a spot at a grand exhibition at the Mall Galleries, featuring a mother of two who never dreamed of being an artist and a student inspired by his grandparents. [S]</desc>
<title>Show Me the Monet</title>
<end>1545</end>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Britain. Fermanagh: The Hairy Bikers get on their bikes to find the best of each county's larder. Si and Dave explore Fermanagh, where they cook a traditional county favourite at Crom Castle. [S]</desc>
<title>The Hairy Bikers' Food Tour of...</title>
<end>1630</end>
<start>1545</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Swindon</subtitle>
<desc>Paul Martin and the Flog It team arrive in Swindon to value the public's antiques with help from experts David Barby and Will Axon. [S]</desc>
<title>Flog It!</title>
<end>1715</end>
<start>1630</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The competition is too close to call between Charles Hanson and fellow auctioneer Jonathan Pratt. Each is determined to track down antiques and make a profit at auction. [S]</desc>
<title>Antiques Road Trip</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1715</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jeremy Vine hosts a general knowledge quiz in which teams from all over the UK battle to beat the Eggheads. [S]</desc>
<title>Eggheads</title>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/4. Nick Hewer helps struggling farms diversify. Nick visits Tullyveery House, where the cattle and sheep herds are no longer enough to support the estate. [S]</desc>
<title>The Farm Fixer</title>
<end>1900</end>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Stories of the Olympic Games. 3/4. 1500 Metres: History of the Olympics through the stories of athletes. A look at the diverse environments and characters that shaped the 1500m. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Faster Higher Stronger -...</title>
<end>2000</end>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/4. Kate Humble and Professor Iain Stewart present live from Kilauea on Hawaii. They explore how our active planet triggers eruptions, earthquakes and tsunamis. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Volcano Live</title>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>6/6. Arnold Circus: Series on how London has changed since Charles Booth's 1886 survey. Arnold Circus, in the East End, is home to the first council estate, which opened in 1896. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>The Secret History of Our Streets</title>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Mark Kermode is in Bexhill-on-Sea, the setting for a new sculpture from artist Richard Wilson which recreates the final scene in cult movie The Italian Job. [S]</desc>
<title>The Culture Show</title>
<end>2230</end>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In-depth investigation and analysis of the stories behind the day's headlines with Gavin Esler. [S] Followed by weather.</desc>
<title>Newsnight</title>
<end>2320</end>
<start>2230</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/3. Wildlife series. Steve Backshall descends into the crater of a giant extinct volcano in New Guinea which biologists have long believed could be home to spectacular new creatures. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Lost Land of the Volcano</title>
<end>0020</end>
<start>2320</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>BBC Two joins the BBC's rolling news channel, with bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<end>0400</end>
<start>0020</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/3. Key Stage 3: Kids journey into the mathematical world that underpins their favourite sport. Romario and Hayden visit the Arsenal training centre to take on a prediction challenge. [S]</desc>
<title>3, 2, 1, Go!</title>
<end>0500</end>
<start>0400</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Six short films presented by Professor Marcus du Sautoy that each begin with a mystery, to be explained by a mathematical concept. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>The Code</title>
<end>0530</end>
<start>0500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Designed for GCSE Business Studies students, the programme goes backstage at a music festival to explain five important business concepts. Presented by Radio 1's Greg James. [S]</desc>
<title>Music, Mud and Making Money</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0530</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sculptures and Snowman: Pingu welcomes viewers to his secret whale-shaped funhouse for sketches and two classic episodes: Pingu's Ice Sculptures and Pingu and the Abominable Snowman. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
