<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Wed Jul 11 08:39:53 2012 -->
<channel id="five" source="XMLTV" date="11/07/2012">
  <programme>
<subtitle>Play Time</subtitle>
<desc>Railway adventures. Famous opera singer Alicia Botti arrives on Sodor. Thomas is bubbling with pride when he is sent to take her to a grand concert.</desc>
<title>Thomas and Friends</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Spring Wotty</subtitle>
<desc>DottyWot loses a bouncing competition, much to her disappointment. Maybe one of the animals in the zoo can help her to win next time?</desc>
<title>The WotWots</title>
<end>0620</end>
<start>0610</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Animation. Who is going around the city hitting people on the head with a small, hard, round object? Max is determined to find out...</desc>
<title>City of Friends</title>
<end>0635</end>
<start>0620</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Royal Roommate</subtitle>
<desc>Animated adventures. Bello helps the King combat his fear of the night when the Queen kicks him out of the castle due to his weird sleeping patterns.</desc>
<title>Jelly Jamm</title>
<end>0645</end>
<start>0635</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Animated series. Granny and Grandpa Pig have invited Peppa and her family to lunch. On the way, Peppa's family get caught in a very long traffic jam.</desc>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0650</end>
<start>0645</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Weeds</subtitle>
<desc>While Farm Girl and Piggy weed the overgrown potato patch, Leonard is at the seaside searching for pearls. But the seaweed he brings back is much more useful.</desc>
<title>Castle Farm</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0650</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Regal larks. Little Princess and her friends go to the seaside. Everyone is disappointed to find the beach empty, and worse still it's raining!</desc>
<title>Little Princess</title>
<end>0710</end>
<start>0700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Visiting the Marigolds</subtitle>
<desc>Impish animation. Mishap follows mishap as everyone pays a visit to snooty King and Queen Marigold's castle.</desc>
<title>Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom</title>
<end>0720</end>
<start>0710</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Picnics</subtitle>
<desc>Mr Stubborn and Mr Fussy visit the beach despite the stormy weather, while Miss Daredevil chooses to go to the Moon with her picnic.</desc>
<title>Mr Men</title>
<end>0730</end>
<start>0720</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>A look ahead to today's children's programmes, including competitions and dedications.</desc>
<title>Milkshake</title>
<end>0735</end>
<start>0730</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Percy and the Monster of Brendam</subtitle>
<desc>Train fun. On the island of Sodor, the fog is beginning to swirl into Brendam Docks. Percy is there, listening to one of Salty's tales!</desc>
<title>Thomas and Friends</title>
<end>0745</end>
<start>0735</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Noddy's Pet Chicken</subtitle>
<desc>Children's animated series. Noddy wants a pet and so he takes a chicken home. However, it proves harder to look after than expected.</desc>
<title>Make Way For Noddy</title>
<end>0800</end>
<start>0745</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Animation about a flower girl and her friends. The twins spot what they think is a fairy at the end of the garden.</desc>
<title>Fifi and The Flowertots</title>
<end>0810</end>
<start>0800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Pig tales. Madame Gazelle takes Peppa and her friends on a train ride, where they must tick off what they see on their activity sheets.</desc>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0815</end>
<start>0810</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Babysitting</subtitle>
<desc>Animated series about a lovable little pig. Mummy and Daddy Pig go out for the evening, leaving Granny and Grandpa Pig to babysit an excitable Peppa and George.</desc>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0825</end>
<start>0815</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Ballet Lesson</subtitle>
<desc>Animated series about a lovable little pig. Peppa is excited about her first ballet lesson.</desc>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<end>0830</end>
<start>0825</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Big Chris Forgets</subtitle>
<desc>Animated adventures of the cheerful racing car. It is Marsha's birthday and Big Chris is in charge of organising a surprise for her.</desc>
<title>Roary The Racing Car</title>
<end>0840</end>
<start>0830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Invisible</subtitle>
<desc>Sesame Street's Bert and Ernie are asked to look after a little girl at a friend's house - but it's hard to keep an eye on her, as she's invisible!</desc>
<title>Bert and Ernie</title>
<end>0845</end>
<start>0840</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>The Camping Trip</subtitle>
<desc>Animation. Rat decides to sell his old camping gear. Who would be daft enough to buy such rubbish? The Bananas, of course! B1 and B2 take the Teddies on a trip.</desc>
<title>Bananas In Pyjamas</title>
<end>0858</end>
<start>0845</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Preschool series following inquisitive puppet Milkshake Monkey. Milkshake Monkey goes miniature with a model village.</desc>
<title>Milkshake Monkey</title>
<end>0900</end>
<start>0858</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Prehistoric animation. Igam Ogam wants everyone to listen to her making music.</desc>
<title>Igam Ogam</title>
<end>0915</end>
<start>0900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Lively magazine show in which Matthew Wright and guests discuss the topical issues of the day.</desc>
<title>The Wright Stuff</title>
<end>1110</end>
<start>0915</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Fishing adventure show. Robson Green travels the globe but will he succeed in catching the fish said to be in the foreign waters?</desc>
<title>Extreme Fishing With Robson Green</title>
<end>1210</end>
<start>1110</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and International news update.</desc>
<title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
<end>1215</end>
<start>1210</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Coverage of all the latest goings-on from inside the Big Brother house.</desc>
<title>Big Brother</title>
<end>1315</end>
<start>1215</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Alf urges Roo to make sure that Lottie is OK. Casey is avoiding home, opting to stay at Sasha's. She is excited, hoping that their friendship can be taken to the next level.</desc>
<title>Home and Away</title>
<end>1345</end>
<start>1315</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jade presents evidence about Troy's violent past at the court case. Ajay argues there is no solid evidence. Furthermore, he raises the issue of Sonya's violent history.</desc>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<end>1415</end>
<start>1345</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Seeing Red</subtitle>
<desc>Crime drama. Jane butts heads with a spiritualist who claims to have intimate knowledge of a woman's murder. (7/23)</desc>
<title>The Mentalist</title>
<end>1515</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Sentimental romantic tale. A US soldier serving in Afghanistan (Johnny Messner) becomes a father-figure to a lonely boy who writes to him from back home in California. (2010)</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<title>Soldier's Love Story</title>
<end>1700</end>
<start>1515</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and International news update.</desc>
<title>5 News at 5</title>
<end>1730</end>
<start>1700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jade presents evidence about Troy's violent past at the court case. Ajay argues there is no solid evidence. Furthermore, he raises the issue of Sonya's violent history.</desc>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1730</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Alf urges Roo to make sure that Lottie is OK. Casey is avoiding home, opting to stay at Sasha's. She is excited, hoping that their friendship can be taken to the next level.</desc>
<title>Home and Away</title>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and International news update.</desc>
<title>5 News at 6.30</title>
<end>1900</end>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Rise of the Rookies</subtitle>
<desc>Extreme truck-driving competition. Dave and Lisa deal with their malfunctioning truck, racing against the clock to make sure they deliver their load on time.</desc>
<title>Ice Road Truckers: Deadliest Roads</title>
<end>1958</end>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and International news update.</desc>
<title>5 News at 19.58</title>
<end>2000</end>
<start>1958</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>With interviews with engineers and practical demonstrations, this film provides the ultimate explanation of how ingenious technology has enabled the biggest metro system in the world, the Tube.</desc>
<title>Building The London Underground</title>
<end>2058</end>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>National and International news update.</desc>
<title>5 News at 20.58</title>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2058</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Baltimore</subtitle>
<desc>US crime drama series. When Tony's former partner is found murdered and linked to the Port-to-Port serial killer, Tony remembers his days as a detective in Baltimore.</desc>
<title>NCIS</title>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Coverage of all the latest goings-on from inside the Big Brother house.</desc>
<title>Big Brother</title>
<end>2300</end>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Emma Willis hosts a round-up of Big Brother-related news and debate, with special guests, exclusive footage and behind the scenes treats.</desc>
<title>Big Brother's Bit On The Side</title>
<end>0000</end>
<start>2300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>High-stakes cash game with a twist. A group of the world's best professional poker players plays alongside top amateurs, plus a player who has qualified online.</desc>
<title>Pokerstars: The Big Game</title>
<end>0100</end>
<start>0000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Live interactive gaming featuring roulette, blackjack and autowheel. For more information and to register visit www.SuperCasino.com.</desc>
<title>Super Casino</title>
<end>0355</end>
<start>0100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Tim Marlow looks at the work of the Western world's most famous artists. The Dutch painter Vermeer who today is considered as great a talent as Rembrandt.</desc>
<title>Great Artists</title>
<end>0420</end>
<start>0355</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Documentary series about the work of dedicated animal lovers who save injured and orphaned wild animals brought into their sanctuary.</desc>
<title>Wildlife SOS</title>
<end>0445</end>
<start>0420</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Documentary series about the work of dedicated animal lovers who save injured and orphaned wild animals brought into their sanctuary.</desc>
<title>Wildlife SOS</title>
<end>0510</end>
<start>0445</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Home improvement series. Alistair Appleton and Californian interior designer Ann Maurice are in Cheltenham.</desc>
<title>House Doctor</title>
<end>0535</end>
<start>0510</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Ann Maurice presents more home improvements for properties that are proving difficult to sell. A divorcing couple must revamp their Victorian semi in Camberley, Surrey.</desc>
<title>House Doctor</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0535</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Thomas and the Pigs</subtitle>
<desc>Railway adventures. Farmer Trotter asks Thomas to collect some straw for the piglets, which are soon to be born.</desc>
<title>Thomas and Friends</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
