<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Sat Jul  7 07:19:20 2012 -->
<channel id="bbc2" source="XMLTV" date="12/07/2012">
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sculptures and Snowman: Pingu welcomes viewers to his secret whale-shaped funhouse for sketches and two classic episodes: Pingu's Ice Sculptures and Pingu and the Abominable Snowman. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Zigby and the Sandcastle: The adventures of Zigby the Zebra and his friends. When Zara's sandcastle disappears, Zigby promises to find out where it's gone. [S]</desc>
<title>Zigby</title>
<end>0625</end>
<start>0610</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Count on Timmy: Animated adventures of a young lamb at nursery school. Timmy and Finlay both have their hearts set on a toy plane, so they try to raise enough buttons to buy it. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Timmy Time</title>
<end>0635</end>
<start>0625</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Creepy Crawly: Animated series about dirtgirl and her friends. Once a year, beneath the golden glow of the harvest moon, the most wonderful thing happens: the Creepy Crawly Concert. [S]</desc>
<title>dirtgirlworld</title>
<end>0650</end>
<start>0635</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Toots Re-routes: Stop-motion series featuring a crime-fighting special agent who plays in a reggae band. Odd diversions prevent a musical legend from performing with the Easy Crew. [S]</desc>
<title>Rastamouse</title>
<end>0700</end>
<start>0650</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Animal action with Johny Pitts and Rani Price. With a baby boom in the parks, which is the cutest? And meet the disabled lioness and find out why she had swimming lessons as a cub. [S]</desc>
<title>Roar</title>
<end>0730</end>
<start>0700</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. Evil-est in Show: Animation. Voltar enters Doomageddon in the neighbourhood pet contest, where he meets his match in a particularly vicious bunny. [S] Followed by Leon.</desc>
<title>League of Super Evil</title>
<end>0745</end>
<start>0730</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. One of Our Castles Is Missing: When Castle Frankenstein disappears, Nine makes a new life for himself in the village. [S] Followed by The Owl.</desc>
<title>Frankenstein's Cat</title>
<end>0800</end>
<start>0745</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBBC. 19/20. Wildlife show. Brayden and Carina handle wriggling reptiles, and Harriet and Luke have a go at being donkey doctors. [S]</desc>
<title>Dick 'N' Dom Go Wild</title>
<end>0830</end>
<start>0800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 18/25. Monster Hunt: Show for preschool children. Nina joins Anna and Keir at Loch Ness to find the monster, as they don't know which sense would be most use in finding Nessie. [S]</desc>
<title>Nina and the Neurons</title>
<end>0845</end>
<start>0830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. The Biggest Story: The comic adventures of two unlikely best friends. Big wants to write a story just for Small. Big, however, cannot find the right words to put onto the paper. [S]</desc>
<title>Big and Small</title>
<end>0900</end>
<start>0845</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Why Zebra Has Stripes: Stories telling a young audience how animals got their distinctive parts. Zebra tries on a black coat to hide better in the savannah, but it is too tight. [S]</desc>
<title>Tinga Tinga Tales</title>
<end>0910</end>
<start>0900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 11/13. Charley's Shadow: Series about a teddy bear with a big imagination. Charley's shadow starts off as a fun playmate but soon causes him problems. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Little Charley Bear</title>
<end>0920</end>
<start>0910</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Raa Raa's Big Book of Noises: Animation featuring Raa Raa, who lives in the Jingly Jangly Jungle. Topsy sets out to make her own book for story time, but it all goes wrong. [S]</desc>
<title>Raa Raa the Noisy Lion</title>
<end>0930</end>
<start>0920</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. 10/15. Benny's Back: Benny and Scrambler want to delay Farmer Pickles and his hay delivery, to help out Bob. [S]</desc>
<title>Bob the Builder: Project Build It</title>
<end>0940</end>
<start>0930</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Sammy's Spoons: The adventures of Frank and Buster, two intrepid koalas in the Australian outback. Mitzi offends Sammy when she says that the spoons are not a real instrument. [S]</desc>
<title>The Koala Brothers</title>
<end>0950</end>
<start>0940</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Moonport Blues: Preschool stop-frame animation set on the second-to-last moon of the Milky Way. Jim and Ripple install new blue landing lights at the moonport. [S]</desc>
<title>Lunar Jim</title>
<end>1000</end>
<start>0950</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Tent: Series in which a drawn line creates challenges for the little character Dipdap. The line draws Dipdap a tent, but each time he settles down, he is disturbed by a creature. [S]</desc>
<title>Dipdap</title>
<end>1005</end>
<start>1000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. The Toy Factory Track: Children's quiz. The Kerwhizz Ker-westion characters have their own toy factory. Which of the three terrific teams will find their way past the many machines? [S]</desc>
<title>Kerwhizz</title>
<end>1030</end>
<start>1005</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Guess What: Driver Dan goes on an exciting journey to Story Corner. Loopy wants to join in a mime game but he's not very good at mime because he can never stay silent. [S]</desc>
<title>Driver Dan's Story Train</title>
<end>1040</end>
<start>1030</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Fireflies: Animated series set in the magical land of Nara. Yojojo plays his pipes to charm a firefly out of its tree hollow and into his paper lantern. [S]</desc>
<title>Waybuloo</title>
<end>1100</end>
<start>1040</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Where Are the Wottingers?: The Pontipines go to meet the Wottingers. The Wottingers are not in. Where could they be? The Pontipines go looking for them around the garden. [S]</desc>
<title>In the Night Garden</title>
<end>1130</end>
<start>1100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>The latest international news from the BBC. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC World News</title>
<end>1200</end>
<start>1130</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Andrew Neil and Jo Coburn with the latest political news, interviews and debate. [S]</desc>
<title>Daily Politics</title>
<end>1300</end>
<start>1200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>6/15. Burghley House: Dr Jonathan Foyle scales Britain's most iconic structures to reveal the buildings' secrets. Jonathan's journey takes him to Burghley House in Lincolnshire. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Climbing Great Buildings</title>
<end>1330</end>
<start>1300</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Sidmouth</subtitle>
<desc>Property series. Jonny Benarr and Ed Hall have an unusual day in Sidmouth, going house hunting and swimming. [S]</desc>
<title>To Buy or Not to Buy</title>
<end>1415</end>
<start>1330</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Anne Robinson presents the quick-fire general knowledge quiz in which contestants must decide at the end of each round which of their number should be eliminated. [S]</desc>
<title>The Weakest Link</title>
<end>1500</end>
<start>1415</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>4/15. Competition for a spot at a grand exhibition at the Royal College of Art, featuring a former engineer, an ambitious teenage sculptor and an 18-year-old English student. [S]</desc>
<title>Show Me the Monet</title>
<end>1545</end>
<start>1500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Britain. Cheshire: The Hairy Bikers get on their bikes to find the best of each county's larder. Si and Dave explore Cheshire, where they visit a smokehouse. [S]</desc>
<title>The Hairy Bikers' Food Tour of...</title>
<end>1630</end>
<start>1545</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<subtitle>Tavistock</subtitle>
<desc>The Flog It team travel to sunny Tavistock. Just down the road in Buckfastleigh, presenter Paul Martin pops into the pub that never called time. [S]</desc>
<title>Flog It!</title>
<end>1715</end>
<start>1630</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Auctioneer Jonathan Pratt is determined to spend, spend, spend, as he and rival Charles Hanson tear around Chorley, Leyland and Preston buying and selling antiques. [S]</desc>
<title>Antiques Road Trip</title>
<end>1800</end>
<start>1715</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Jeremy Vine hosts a general knowledge quiz in which teams from all over the UK battle to beat the Eggheads. [S]</desc>
<title>Eggheads</title>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>4/4. Nick Hewer helps struggling farms diversify. Nick tries to get a farm and tearoom to work together to create new products. [S]</desc>
<title>The Farm Fixer</title>
<end>1900</end>
<start>1830</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>...Stories of the Olympic Games. 4/4. Swimming: A history of the Olympics through the stories of athletes. A look at the evolution of swimming and its four different strokes. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>Faster Higher Stronger -...</title>
<end>2000</end>
<start>1900</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>4/4. Kate Humble and Professor Iain Stewart present live from Kilauea on Hawaii. Broadcasting from the summit crater, they look to the future of volcanic forecasting. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Volcano Live</title>
<end>2100</end>
<start>2000</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>3/3. Jacques Peretti examines assumptions about what is and is not healthy. He also looks at how product marketing can seduce consumers into buying supposed 'healthy foods'. Also in HD. [AD,S]</desc>
<title>The Men Who Made Us Fat</title>
<end>2200</end>
<start>2100</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>5/13. Topical comedy. Dara O Briain and regulars Chris Addison, Hugh Dennis and Andy Parsons look back over the week's events with guests Josh Widdicombe and Miles Jupp. [S]</desc>
<title>Mock the Week</title>
<end>2230</end>
<start>2200</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>In-depth investigation and analysis of the stories behind the day's headlines with Eddie Mair. [S] Followed by weather.</desc>
<title>Newsnight</title>
<end>2320</end>
<start>2230</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Hazel Irvine presents highlights of the first day's action from Castle Stuart. Luke Donald returns to defend his title, with Padraig Harrington and Louis Oosthuizen also competing. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
<title>Golf: Scottish Open Highlights</title>
<end>0020</end>
<start>2320</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Mark Kermode is in Bexhill-on-Sea, the setting for a new sculpture from artist Richard Wilson which recreates the final scene in cult movie The Italian Job. [S]</desc>
<title>The Culture Show</title>
<end>0050</end>
<start>0020</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>BBC Two joins the BBC's rolling news channel, with bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes. [S]</desc>
<title>BBC News</title>
<end>0400</end>
<start>0050</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Explores the British legal system in a new way, as young people from UK state schools take on the roles of barrister, defendant, witness, jury, court reporter and court artist. [S]</desc>
<title>Young Legal Eagles</title>
<end>0500</end>
<start>0400</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>Short dramas in the Bafta-winning series about the journey from primary to secondary school. The programme explores peer culture and peer pressure, homework and bullying. [S]</desc>
<title>L8R Youngers 2</title>
<end>0540</end>
<start>0500</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>2/4. Charles Dickens hosts a chat show looking at 19th-century topics. In this episode, he is joined by Mary Seacole and Florence Nightingale to discuss Victorian health. [S]</desc>
<title>The Charles Dickens Show: Health</title>
<end>0600</end>
<start>0540</start>
  </programme>
  <programme>
<desc>CBeebies. Moon and Snowboarding: Pingu welcomes viewers to his secret whale-shaped funhouse for another show. The episodes are Pingu's Moon Adventure and Robby the Snowboarder. [S]</desc>
<title>The Pingu Show</title>
<end>0610</end>
<start>0600</start>
  </programme>
</channel>
